(Stuart:)the high contrast
of zebra stripes might provide
(Stuart:)better stimulus
for a developing baby.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, you're probably right,
go with the zebras.
(Stuart:)Good choice, boss.
(Raj:)At least my nose
is naturally brown.
(Bernadette:)Hey, could you please go
to the market for me?
(Howard:)Get Stuart or Raj to do it.
(Bernadette:)Howie, they've been doing
everything for you.
(Howard:)Mm, I know.
(Howard:)It's really making me
lose respect for both of them.
(Bernadette:)Please just go to the store.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Howard:)Who wants to drive me
to the store?
- Me!
- I'll do it!
(Bernadette:)Take Raj.
(Bernadette:)Stuart is supposed
to paint my toenails.
(Raj:)What do you think?
(Penny:)Should we go to a hotel?
(Leonard:)And just leave
him here alone?